胡说什么  大白
That's nonsense, Baymax.
我没事
I'm doing just fine.
凯斯婶婶  你有毯子吗
Hey, uh, Aunt Cass, do you have a blanket?
还需要附送枕头吗
You want a pillow with that blanket?
不用了
We're covered.
一条毯子  不要枕头  马上来
One blanket, hold the pillow, coming up.
伙计们  伙计们  伙计们  伙计们  伙计们
Guys! Guys! Guys! Guys! Guys! Guys! Guys! Guys! Guys! Guys!
伙计们  伙计们  伙计们  伙计们
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys!
冷静点  伙计  你想对我们说什么
Calm down, boy! What are you trying to tell us?
旧京山出现了一个怪兽
There's a monster in San Fransokyo!
特大新闻  旧京山出现了一个
Breaking news. Reports of what is described as a "Monster"
游荡的怪兽
is loose in San Fransokyo.
请注意  我们没有确凿的目击证据
Please note, we have no hard evidence to support this claim.
但是我重复
But I repeat,
旧京山出现一个游荡的怪兽
a monster is loose in San Fransokyo!